I have a question. Why can't a robot
just click I'm not a robot? Turns out
that the answer to that question is part
of a bigger story about being human. The
tech is called reCAPTCHA. It stands for
completely automated public Turing test
to tell computers and humans apart. You
might remember some of these older
versions, or these. Robots are pretty
good at those ones now, but the box test
isn't really about the box. It's
tracking all kinds of other things about
your behavior. Like, for example, where
you put the mouse before you click the
box. Robots move like this.
But humans move kind of like this.
In other words, these tests aren't about
what makes humans better than robots.
They're about what makes humans human.
That's not new. It's the same question
we've been thinking about for centuries.
And in a world where technology can do
more and more surprising things, I think
there's something kind of beautiful
about constantly trying to figure out
what makes us differentiatedly human. If
you like optimistic science and tech
stories, [music] follow for more.